Finding Aid for the Nancy Malone Papers PASC.0254
UCLA Library Special Collections
- Directing
  - unspecified
    - Hotel - Pressure Points, 1986 (Box 22, Folder 4)
      Final draft script, revision outline, production material and set plans.
    - Hotel - Promises to Keep, 1985 (Box 22, Folder 5)
      Third draft script, production material and set plans.
    - Hotel - Recriminations, 1985 (Box 23, Folder 1)
    - Hotel - Cry Wolf, 1985 (Box 23, Folder 2)
    - Resurrection Blvd - El Mejor Amigo Del Hombre, 2001 (Box 23, Folder 3)
      Revised script, production material and stage plans.
    - Resurrection Blvd - La Guerra de Bibi, 2001 (Box 23, Folder 4)
      Two revised scripts, production material, and stage plans.
    - Resurrection Blvd - El Que Necesita, 2001 (Box 23, Folder 5)
      Revised script, production material and set plans.
    - Resurrection Blvd - Con Ciudado, 2001 (Box 24, Folder 1)
    - Resurrection Blvd - Hermanos (folder 1 of 2), 2000 (Box 24, Folder 2)
      Two scripts, one with title page signed by persons associated with the production, and production material.
    - Resurrection Blvd - Hermanos (folder 2 of 2), 2000 (Box 24, Folder 3)
      Script, photographs and production material. With a publicity still signed by cast members.
    - Resurrection Blvd - Revalaciones, 2000 (Box 24, Folder 4)
      Script with title page signed by people associated with the production, production material and set plans.
    - Melrose Place - Promise Broken (A), 1992 Aug (Box 24, Folder 5)
      Shooting draft script, production material, set plans and what appears to be location snap shots,.
    - Melrose Place - Bitch is Back (The), 1994 Mar (Box 25, Folder 1)
    - Melrose Place - Swept Away, 1994 Jan (Box 25, Folder 2)
      Script, production material and set plans.
    - Melrose Place - Much Ado About Everything, 1993 July (Box 25, Folder 3)
      Scripts, production material, and set plans.
    - Melrose Place - No Bed of Roses, 1993 Aug (Box 25, Folder 4)
      Script, production material, and set plans.
    - Melrose Place - Strange Bedfellows, 1993 Oct (Box 26, Folder 2)
      Script material, production material, set plans, and TV Guide (Feb 1994).
    - Heart Beat - Stress, 1988 (Box 26, Folder 3)
    - Heart Beat - Our Trespasses, 1988 (Box 26, Folder 4)
      Final draft script, treatment, production material and set plans.
    - Melrose Place - deal memos, 1992 Aug-Jan 1994 (Box 26, Folder 5)
    - Melrose Place - Irreconcilable Similarities, 1993 Jan (Box 27, Folder 1)
      Script material, production material, and set plans.
    - Melrose Place - Picture Imperfect, 1992 Nov (Box 27, Folder 2)
      Pink revised and green revised shooting scripts, production material, and set plans.
    - Dawson's Creek - Family Way (A), 2000 Sep (Box 27, Folder 3)
      Revised blue script with title page signed by people involved in the production, production material, snapshots, set plans, Capeside High School diploma made out to Nancy Malone.
    - Cagney and Lacey - Yup, 1988 Mar (Box 27, Folder 4)
      Two scripts, production material, photographs, and Hollywood Reporter from March 8 1988.
    - Home Song CBS movie of the week (folder 1 of 3), 1995 Oct (Box 28, Folder 1)
      Scripts, photographic material and thank you notes.
    - Home Song CBS movie of the week (folder 2 of 3), 1995 Oct (Box 28, Folder 2)
      Production material and clippings.
    - Home Song CBS movie of the week (folder 3 of 3), 1995 Oct (Box 28, Folder 3)
      Production material.
    - I Married A Monster (folder 1 of 2), 1998 Jan 1998 (Box 28, Folder 4)
      Revised script.
    - I Married a Monster (folder 2 of 2), 1997 Oct-July 1998 (Box 28, Folder 5)
    - I Married A Monster, 1997-1998 (Box 29, Folder 1)
      Photographs, clippings story boards, and art work.
    - I Married A Monster, 1998 May- June (Box 29, Folder 2)
      Script material, production material, set plans, story boards, and thank you notes.
    - I Married A Monster, 1998 Mar - Sept (Box 29, Folder 3)
    - Star Trek - comments on Nancy Malone shows, 1997, 2006 (Box 29, Folder 4)
      Electronic correspondence.
    - I Married A Monster, 1998 April - July (Box 30, Folder 1)
      Production material with particular emphasis on budget information.
    - Melrose Place - Peanut Butter and Jealousy, 1992 Dec (Box 30, Folder 2)
      Green revised script, production material, and set plans.
    - Melrose Place - House of God, 1992 Sept (Box 30, Folder 3)
      Pink and blue revised shooting draft scripts, first draft script, production material and set plans.
    - General Hospital - remote shots, 1991 June 19 (Box 30, Folder 4)
      Production information. Tank you letter from Nancy Malone dated Sept. 30, 1983.
    - Parent's License (The), 1991 Jul (Box 30, Folder 5)
      Final shooting script, facsimile concept sketches, and production material.
    - Star Trek - Message in a Bottle, 1997 Sept-Nov (Box 31, Folder 1)
      Final draft script, production material, and set plans
    - Star Trek - Coda, 1996 Oct-Nov (Box 31, Folder 2)
      Final draft script, production material, additional script material and newsletter of the Kate Mulgreen Appreciation Society.
    - Running Dragon - Lock and Load Babe, 1994 Dec (Box 31, Folder 3)
      Episode also known as One Shot Deal. Final draft script and production material.
    - Key West - Compadres, 1992 Oct-Nov (Box 31, Folder 4)
      Final draft script, production material and snapshots.
    - Touched by an Angel - Operation Smile, 1995 September (Box 32, Folder 1)
      Yellow revised script, production materials, and snapshots.
    - Fame L.A. - Guru (The), 1997 Aug-Oct (Box 32, Folder 2)
    - Sisters - Crash and Born, 1992 Sept - Nov, 1993 July - Aug (Box 32, Folder 3)
      Writer's third draft script, set plans, clippings, Emmy nomination letter and congratulatory notes.
    - Judging Amy - Who Shot Dick, 2001 Nov (Box 32, Folder 4)
    - Pickett Fences - Upbringings, 1995 Mar-April (Box 32, Folder 5)
      Revised draft script, production material, and set plans.
    - Shades of L.A. - Dummy Up, 1990 Aug-Sep (Box 33, Folder 1)
      Episode also known as Big Brother is Watching. Four scripts and production materials.
    - Guardian (The) - Legacy (folder 1 of 4), 2003 Oct (Box 33, Folder 2)
      Revised yellow script and production material.
    - Guardian (The) - Legacy (folder 2 of 4), 2003 June (Box 33, Folder 3)
      Director set plans.
    - Guardian (The) - Legacy (folder 3 of 4), 2003 Oct-Nov (Box 33, Folder 4)
      Production information.
    - Guardian (The) -Legacy (folder 4 of 4), 2003 Sep-Nov (Box 33, Folder 5)
      Photocopy of revised green script, snapshots and letter of employment.
    - Cry for an Angel - photographs, no date (Box 33, Folder 6)
    - Beverly Hills 90210 - Nancy Susan Reynolds award program, 1991 Nov 12 (Box 33, Folder 7)
      Malone is honoree.
    - Starman - Different Drummers, 1986 Aug (Box 34, Folder 1)
      Revised final draft script, production material, set plans and snapshots.
    - Starman - Different Drummers, 1986 Aug 6 (Box 34, Folder 2)
      Script.
    - Merlene of the Movies, 1980 Sept 2 (Box 34, Folder 3)
      Two copies of revised script and production material.
    - Run, 1970 Sept - Dec, 1977 Nov 4 (Box 34, Folder 4)
      Synopsis, letter to parents, receipts.
    - Pride 1 and 2, 1984 Jul - Aug (Box 34, Folder 5)
      Also produced by Malone. Fourth draft script, snapshots, production material and set plans.
    - Perfect Day for Bananafish (A) photographs, no date (Box 34, Folder 6)
      Produced for the AFI Directing Workshop for Women.
    - Perfect Day for Bananafish (A), 1982 Jul - Aug (Box 34, Folder 7)
      Produced for the AFI Directing Workshop for Women. Script and production material.
    - Burning Zone - Elegy for a Dream, 1997 Jan (Box 36, Folder 1)
      Revised script and production material.
    - Central Park West - # 20, 1996 Feb (Box 36, Folder 2)
      Revised blue script, photography with Raquel Welch and Malone, production material and set plans.
    - Shades of L.A. - Concrete Evidence, 1990 Jul - Aug (Box 36, Folder 3)
    - Beverly Hills 90210 - Isn't it Romantic?, 1990 Oct - Nov (Box 36, Folder 4)
      Revised final draft script, final draft script and production material.
    - Perfect Day for Bananafish (A), 1982 Jul - Aug (Box 36, Folder 5)
    - Trials of Rosie O'Neill (The) - Heart Break Hotel, 1992 Jun - Aug (Box 36, Folder 6)
      44th Annual Primetime Emmy Awards Program and clippings.
    - Perfect Day for Bananafish (A), 1982 Jul - Aug (Box 37, Folder 1)
      Three scripts and script material.
    - Perfect Day for Bananafish (A), 1982 Jul - Aug (Box 37, Folder 2)
      Production reports, camera reports and editor's notes.
    - Merlene of the Movies, 1980-1984 (Box 37, Folder 3)
      Revised script, photographs, certificate of copyright registration, Malone motion picture agreement and production material.
    - Merlene of the Movies, 1980 Jul - Sep (Box 37, Folder 4)
      Revised script, photographs, award notifications, correspondence and production material.
    - Merlene of the Movies, 1980 Jul - Aug, 1982 Apr - Jul (Box 37, Folder 5)
      Revised script, photographs, film festival correspondence and production material.
    - Trouble in the Works, 1981 Mar - May (Box 37, Folder 6)
      Produced for the AFI Directing Workshop for Women. Photographs, script material and production material.
    - Merlene of the Movies, 1980 Sept, 1982 Jun - Sep (Box 38, Folder 1)
      Three revised scripts, film festival award notifications, film festival correspondence, film synopses, press, actor headshots, snapshots and film agreements.
    - Merlene of the Movies - photographs and contact sheets, no date (Box 38, Folder 2)
      Contact sheets appear to go with negatives in box 38 folder 3.
    - Merlene of the Movies - negatives, no date (Box 38, Folder 3)
      Negatives appear to go with contact sheets in box 38 folder 2.
    - Merlene of the Movies - contact sheets and negatives, no date (Box 38, Folder 4)
    - Trials of Rosie O'Neill (The) - The Gangs all Here, 1990 Sep - Oct (Box 38, Folder 5)
      Production draft script, script material and production material.
    - Trials of Rosie O'Neill (The) - Heart Break Hotel, 1991 Nov (Box 39, Folder 1)
    - Bradys (The) - Hat in the Ring, 1990 Jan (Box 39, Folder 2)
      Revised script 1/16/1990, revised script 1/25/1990 and production material.
    - Nightingales - episode four, 1988 Dec - 1989 Jan (Box 39, Folder 3)
    - Nightingales - episode six, 1989 Jan (Box 39, Folder 4)
      Second revised final script, script pages and production material.
    - Knots Landing - 1,001 Nights of Anne Matheson, 1991 Aug (Box 39, Folder 5)
      Final draft script, script material, and production material.
    - Trials of Rosie O'Neill (The) - Reunion, 1990 Dec (Box 40, Folder 1)
      Production draft script and production material.
    - There Were Times, Dear - public relations clipping, 1985 Nov, May-June 1987 (Box 40, Folder 2)
    - There Were Times, Dear - festival awards, 1985, 1986, 1987 (Box 40, Folder 8)
    - There Were Times, Dear - permits for minors, 1987 Jan 26 (Box 41, Folder 1)
    - There Were Times, Dear - Directors production notes, 1985 May - 1985 Oct (Box 41, Folder 2)
    - There Were Times, Dear - SAG info, 1985 Feb, May, Jul (Box 41, Folder 3)
    - There Were Times, Dear - DGA agreements WGA, 1986 Jul - Aug, 1987 Feb (Box 41, Folder 4)
    - There Were Times, Dear - production (folder 1 of 2), 1985 Jun - Jul (Box 41, Folder 4)
      Scripts and production camera reports.
    - There Were Times, Dear - script supervisor report, daily production report, day out of days, 1985 Jul (Box 41, Folder 5)
    - There Were Times, Dear - release forms, 1985 Jul (Box 41, Folder 6)
    - There Were Times, Dear - financing and contributions, 1985 Jul - Aug (Box 41, Folder 7)
    - There Were Times, Dear - legal, 1985 Jun - 1989 Jul (Box 41, Folder 8)
    - There Were Times, Dear - legal research, 1985 Jul- Aug (Box 41, Folder 9)
    - There Were Times, Dear - thanks and credit info, 1985 Jun - Aug (Box 41, Folder 10)
    - There Were Times, Dear - Alzheimer's patients release forms, 1985 Jul - Aug (Box 41, Folder 11)
    - There Were Times, Dear - production budget, 1985 Nov 30 (Box 41, Folder 12)
    - There Were Times, Dear - location photos, 1985 Jun - Aug (Box 41, Folder 13)
      Photographs, location permits and filming permits.
    - There Were Times, Dear - script with director's handwritten notes, 1985 Jun 21 (Box 41, Folder 14)
    - There Were Times, Dear - second draft script with directions handwritten notes, no date (Box 42, Folder 1)
    - There Were Times, Dear - script supervisor's book notes, 1985 Jun - Jul (Box 42, Folder 2)
      Script and production material.
    - There Were Times, Dear - director's notes and scripts, 1985 Jun (Box 42, Folder 3)
    - There Were Times, Dear - production camera reports, 1985 Jul (Box 42, Folder 4)
    - There Were Times, Dear - pr production stills, no date (Box 42, Folder 5)
    - There Were Times, Dear - production stills, no date (Box 42, Folder 6)
    - There Were Times, Dear - AFI screening photos, no date (Box 42, Folder 7)
    - There Were Times, Dear - New England Gerontological Society screening, no date (Box 42, Folder 8)
    - There Were Times, Dear - publicity stills b+w / color cast, no date (Box 42, Folder 9)
    - There Were Times, Dear - crew stills b+w color, no date (Box 43, Folder 1)
    - There Were Times, Dear - crew stills b+w color, no date (Box 43, Folder 1)
    - There Were Times, Dear - post production correspondence, 1985 May - Aug, 1986 Jan (Box 43, Folder 2)
    - There Were Times, Dear -accounting, 1985 Jul - Dec (Box 43, Folder 3)
    - There Were Times, Dear - music, 1985 Jul - 1987 Apr (Box 43, Folder 4)
      `
    - There Were Times, Dear - clearances and residuals, 1985 Jul, 1986 Dec, 1987 Mar - Apr (Box 43, Folder 5)
    - There Were Times, Dear - as broadcast script Sandoz version (2 copies), no date (Box 43, Folder 6)
    - There Were Times, Dear - distribution, 1990 Jun - 1994 Nov (Box 43, Folder 7)
    - There Were Times, Dear - public relations Emmy push, 1987 Mar - June (Box 43, Folder 8)
      Hollywood Reporter issue dated July 7 1987, snapshots, Emmy Magazine issue dated August 1987, Variety Daily issue dated July 14 1987 and original and photocopied clippings.
    - There Were Times, Dear - Nightwatch video, 1987 May 21 (Box 44)
    - There Were Times, Dear - promo video, no date (Box 44)
      There Were Times, Dear 45 second promo video and one minute long Alzheimer's public service announcement.
    - Bob Hope Christmas Show: Hopes for the Holidays - 2 CDs, 1994 Dec 14 (Box 44)
    - Home Song - audio cassette tape, 1995 Dec 29 (Box 44)
      Label reads "Side A: Music Sketches. 2 Side B: Original demo."
    - Parent's License (The) - video, 1991 (Box 44)
    - The Trials of Rosie O'Neill - Heart Break Hotel video, no date (Box 44)
    - World of CRS, The - 2 DVDs, 1982 (Box 44)
    - Agnes of God - audio cassette tape, 2000 (Box 44)
    - Country Girl (The). 2 CDs, 2002 (Box 44)
    - Death of a Miner (The) - audio cassette tape, no date (Box 44)
    - Howie the Rookie - DVD, no date (Box 44)
    - Howie the Rookie - Joe Franklin interviews Nancy Malone. CD., no date (Box 44)
    - Howie the Rookie - sound effects. CD., no date (Box 44)
    - Howie the Rookie - The Kristal Hart Show video, no date (Box 44)
    - Old Times - Tiffany Theatre. CD., 2004 Sep 16 (Box 44)
    - Prelude to a Kiss - audio cassette tape, 2000 (Box 44)
    - Railroad Women - audio cassette tape, no date (Box 44)
    - There Were Times, Dear - public relations clippings, 1984 Apr, 1985-1987 (Box 45, Folder 1)
    - There Were Times, Dear - public relations clippings, Nov 1985, 1987 June (Box 45, Folder 2)
    - There Were Times, Dear - press kit, ca. 1987 June (Box 45, Folder 3)
    - There Were Times, Dear - correspondence, 1987 Jan - April, 1988 March (Box 45, Folder 4)
      With television promotion release waivers signed by Cariou and Jones.
    - There Were Times, Dear - correspondence, Feb 1984 - Jun 1987 (Box 45, Folder 5)
    - There Were Times, Dear - fundraising for Alzheimer's Support Groups, no date (Box 45, Folder 6)
      Drafts of request form, outreach letter, and license agreement.
    - There Were Times, Dear - fundraising events and information, 1986-1987 (Box 45, Folder 7)
      Invitations, thank you notes, and ephemera.
    - There Were Times, Dear - Irish screening letters, 1985 Aug, 1986 May, 1987 Sept (Box 45, Folder 8)
    - There Were Times, Dear - Fundraisers Indiana - press kits, 1988 Oct (Box 45, Folder 9)
    - There Were Times, Dear - publicity, 1985 July, Mar-May 1987 (Box 46, Folder 1)
      Press letters and press kit.
    - There Were Times, Dear - public relations letters, 1987 Jan-Mar (Box 46, Folder 2)
    - There Were Times, Dear - Educational Screenings, 1989 Sept, May-Sept 1990 (Box 46, Folder 3)
      Correspondence and programs.
    - There Were Times, Dear - Sandoz foreign screenings, 1988-1990, 1992 Jan-Mar (Box 46, Folder 4)
      Correspondence (mostly photocopies).
    - There Were Times, Dear - Film Festival entry application forms binder, 1986 (Box 46, Folder 5)
      Binder removed for preservation purposes.
    - Deal Memos, 1977-1978, 1991-1997 (Box 47, Folder 1)
      May include contracts related to producing.
    - There Were Times, Dear - citations and letters of appreciation, 1985-1987, 1989, 1993 (Box 53, Folder 1)
    - There Were Times, Dear - Congressional Clearinghouse on the Future presentation, 1985-1987 (Box 53, Folder 2)
    - There Were Times, Dear - letter from Mayor Ed Koch, 1987 May (Box 53, Folder 3)
    - There Were Times, Dear - Center for the Study of Aging Award program and photographs, 1987 May (Box 53, Folder 4)
    - There Were Times, Dear - citations and proclamation, no date (Box 54, Folder 1)
    - There Were Times, Dear - mounted Variety advertisement and Los Angeles Times piece, 1986 Aug, 1987 May (Box 54, Folder 2)
    - Plight of Women Directors Improved, But Not Much - mounted Los Angeles Times clipping, 1986 Nov (Box 54, Folder 8)
    - Howie the Rookie posters (2 items), 2005 (Box 55, Folder 1)
    - There Were Times, Dear - magazine advertisements, 1987 May-June (Box 58, Folder 5)
      Magazine ads for airing on television.
- Executive
  - unspecified
    - Tomorrow Entertainment - photocopied trade clippings, 1970 (Box 47, Folder 5)
    - 20th Century Fox clippings and photographs, 1975-1976 (Box 47, Folder 6)
    - 20th Century Fox Deal, 1977 (Box 47, Folder 7)
      Interoffice memos.
- General Career
  - unspecified
    - Agents, ca. 1970s-1990s (Box 40, Folder 3)
      Contracts and correspondence mostly from the 1980s.
    - Speech Appearance, no date (Box 40, Folder 7)
      With notes and program for Aaron Spelling Tribute.
    - Clippings, 1960s, 1970s, 1980s, 2002 (Box 40, Folder 9)
      Some of the clippings appear to have been removed from a scrapbook.
    - AFI Directing Workshop for Women - Trouble in the Works letters, 1976 Sept, 1981 Aug-Oct (Box 49, Folder 4)
    - Honors, Awards and Certificates, 1970s, 1990s, 2005 (Box 51, Folder 6)
      Directors Guild of America certificate originally housed in silver frame (gifted to Malone from Joan Collins); frame moved to Box ??
    - Photographs of Malone and others, no date (Box 51, Folder 16)
      With President Bill Clinton, Patty Duke, Robert Joseph, Dean Jones, Norman Lear, Ann Richards, Irwin Shaw, and Dave Tebit. Additionally, photocopied photographs with Ang Lee.
    - Photographs inscribed to Malone, no date (Box 51, Folder 17)
      With Barbara Jordon, Ruby Keeler, and Ann Richards.
    - Professional Education ephemera, 1950s, 2009 and no date (Box 57, Folder 8)
      With notes from Shannon Day and class schedule from Stella Adler Theatre Studio.
    - Understanding the Film: An Introduction to Film Appreciation, 1995 Oct (Box 58, Folder 1)
      Fax communication with Jan Bone.
    - Assorted notes and letters, 1960s, 1970s, 1980s, 2010 (Box 58, Folder 2)
      With notes from Ang Lee and George Deukmegian and note to Ray Bradbury.
    - Irish America magazine, 1992 Mar (Box 58, Folder 3)
      Top one-hundred issue, including Malone.
    - Emmy magazine, 1989 Aug (Box 58, Folder 4)
      Trading Places by Libby Slate. With brief profile about Malone.
    - Photographs with Malone and others related to directing (Box 58, Folder 12)
      Simon Baker, Michel Hugo, and Tony Askins among others.
- Philanthropic Activities
  - unspecified
    - AFI Directing Workshop for Women - First 5 Cycle, 1980s - 1990s (Box 49, Folder 5)
    - Charity Benefit Appearances, 1960s and 1970 (Box 51, Folder 4)
      Letters of appreciation, photographs, and clipping.
    - LA City Film Development Council, 1974 Oct-Nov (Box 51, Folder 5)
      Invitation letter, photograph with former Mayor Tom Bradley, and clipping.
    - American Cinema Editors Award -nomination notification, 1965, 1966 (Box 51, Folder 7)
    - Academy of Motion Picture Arts and Sciences Members' Legacy Gallery - brochure and appeal letter, 1993 June (Box 51, Folder 8)
    - 2nd Annual Small Pictures Independent Film Festival Judge - program, 1997 (Box 58, Folder 7)
    - Firstenberg Luncheon and Award, 2007 (Box 58, Folder 9)
      Firstenberg -- printed material concerning Firstenberg Award and a luncheon in honor of Firstenberg.
- Producing
  - unspecified
    - Imposter (The) (folder 1 of 2), 1984 (Box 13, Folder 1)
      Appears to have also been known as The Snowman and/or The Great Pretender. Script, photographs, clippings and production material.
    - Imposter (The) (folder 2 of 2), 1984 (Box 13, Folder 2)
      Appears to have also been known as The Snowman and/or The Great Pretender. Budget and expense reports, casting information and screening reports.
    - Bob Hope: The First 90 Years - script, 1993 (Box 13, Folder 3)
    - Bob Hope: The First 90 Years (folder 1 of 3), 1993 (Box 13, Folder 4)
      Also produced by Malone. Notes, skit scripts and clip schedules
    - Bob Hope: The First 90 Years (folder 2 of 3), 1993 (Box 14, Folder 1)
      Also produced by Malone. Photocopied and original photographs, interview transcript, and Emmy Awards nomination letter and program.
    - Bob Hope: The First 90 Years (folder 3 of 3), 1993 (Box 14, Folder 2)
      Also produced by Malone. Script, clippings, transcript of tapping, production schedule, and Emmy Magazine.
    - World of CRS (The) - script and closing credits, 1982 Mar 22 (Box 14, Folder 3)
    - Bionic Woman, 1977 (Box 14, Folder 4)
      Clippings, publicity, crew list, end credits used for filming. Signed note from Burt Reynolds.
    - Five Finger Discount (The) (folder 1 of 2), 1977 (Box 14, Folder 5)
      Production material, employment agreements, press and budget summary.
    - Five Finger Discount (The) (folder 2 of 2), 1977 (Box 14, Folder 6)
      Shooting script and production material.
    - Violation of Sarah McDavid (The) -shooting script and production material, 1981 (Box 15, Folder 1)
    - Violation of Sarah McDavid (The) - correspondence and production material., 1981 (Box 15, Folder 2)
    - Violation of Sarah McDavid (The) - photographs and production material, 1981 (Box 15, Folder 3)
    - Womenspeak: The California Commission on the Status of Women, 1973 (Box 15, Folder 4)
      Script, photographs, credits, and issue of Screen Actor magazine (July 1973).
    - Community of Caring: Directors Guild of America, 1998 (Box 15, Folder 5)
      Photographs, Directors Guild of America magazine (June/July 1998), 50th Annual Emmy Awards Program, congratulatory letters, and crew list.
    - Like Mom, Like Me, 1978 (Box 15, Folder 6)